Viewers, the devil’s hand is destruction; his hand is a killer;
I remove the devil’s hand in your life.
In your business, remove the devil;
his hand in your life, business, career, family – remove it, in the name of Jesus!
I bind your spirit with Christ’s Spirit – be bound, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips!
I command healing on you now!
Be healed!
Jesus, every disease, sickness, wound, heal them, in Jesus’ name!
[Amen.]
Heal every disease, infirmity, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
Rejoice!
The Word of God says you are healed.
The Word of God says you are delivered.
[Amen!]
Act it and believe it right now – I am healed, I can see I am healed;
I’m delivered, I can see I’m delivered.
I'm free, I can see I'm free.
I’m blessed, I can see I’m blessed.
Believe it!
Confess it!
Now, you have been bound with Christ’s Spirit; your spirit has been bound with Christ’s Spirit.
I mean, you have been anchored.
Every spirit, thought, be seized, in the name of Jesus!
[Amen!]
Every devil’s assignment against you in whatever way, fail, in the name of Jesus!
Fail!
Begin to shine!
I said, "Begin to shine!"
I cannot hear you, "Begin to shine!"
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God as you send your testimony.
Engage with God.
TT ROBERT BEGIER